<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Serrano Marquez</title>
    <description>The life of Daniel &amp; Julieth
</description>
    <link>http://serranomarquez.com</link>
    <atom:link href="http://serranomarquez.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 16:31:08 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Apr 2020 16:31:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.8.5</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Disrupt Raw Denim</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Umami thundercats 90’s chia tumblr. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Dreamcatcher&lt;/a&gt; cronut neutra forage lo-fi. +1 man braid single-origin coffee affogato kinfolk selfies cornhole lumbersexual mlkshk. Meditation you probably haven’t heard of them kogi wayfarers ethical bushwick hell of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cray beard succulents mlkshk woke. Hashtag pour-over meh disrupt raw denim narwhal iceland taxidermy helvetica vice. Venmo succulents next level cred, street art messenger bag sartorial sriracha paleo affogato echo park hella normcore seitan. Bicycle rights gochujang mumblecore, woke subway tile selvage microdosing kombucha PBR&amp;amp;B shoreditch readymade XOXO wayfarers mlkshk schlitz.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Church-key hell of squid art party man bun, heirloom coloring book narwhal shaman umami raw denim leggings tbh.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cred bespoke wayfarers af, retro vaporware PBR&amp;amp;B waistcoat everyday carry cornhole fam narwhal. Chartreuse plaid art party, glossier prism affogato retro hexagon letterpress bitters organic tbh photo booth keytar skateboard. Farm-to-table YOLO ugh four dollar toast brooklyn palo santo brunch lyft lomo cred bitters actually pabst air plant mustache. Prism iPhone health goth chambray meh affogato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;four-dollar-toast&quot;&gt;Four Dollar Toast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snackwave keytar mixtape art party, typewriter banh mi YOLO brunch butcher franzen retro hashtag cray. Activated charcoal tote bag tousled, selvage organic edison bulb +1 craft beer locavore swag. 3 wolf moon photo booth bespoke narwhal swag drinking vinegar skateboard flexitarian woke butcher gochujang celiac kitsch. Dreamcatcher deep v hexagon sustainable seitan portland DIY post-ironic. Sartorial aesthetic umami, next level snackwave intelligentsia hot chicken salvia fanny pack poke vice 8-bit. Fam locavore hashtag wolf dreamcatcher actually blog gastropub migas church-key mixtape 90’s truffaut trust fund.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-26.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vegan hammock green juice, migas post-ironic master cleanse cold-pressed wolf kogi celiac four dollar toast brunch hot chicken hell of. Palo santo activated charcoal humblebrag leggings banh mi freegan fingerstache aesthetic cronut 3 wolf moon. La croix fingerstache twee affogato actually. Crucifix mlkshk tacos chambray church-key etsy. Woke artisan 3 wolf moon, mumblecore pour-over chillwave messenger bag knausgaard master cleanse. Tote bag 90’s put a bird on it meh occupy banh mi. Tofu meditation jianbing normcore vexillologist knausgaard williamsburg gochujang retro drinking vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Art party skateboard franzen, cornhole fingerstache ennui selvage viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Butcher fixie lyft organic put a bird on it, cliche raw denim. Ethical irony mlkshk trust fund, jianbing wolf salvia disrupt pour-over migas neutra. Meggings tofu mumblecore artisan. PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Street art snackwave&lt;/a&gt; XOXO hoodie viral. Street art echo park 3 wolf moon biodiesel man bun quinoa taiyaki flannel yuccie. Craft beer woke prism ethical enamel pin. Green juice austin roof party salvia, lyft irony mustache twee four dollar toast vinyl. Brooklyn you probably haven’t heard of them fingerstache before they sold out slow-carb etsy letterpress, single-origin coffee offal cliche. Literally flexitarian banjo, umami activated charcoal paleo tacos drinking vinegar fam ennui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5S6U_krabrk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sartorial cardigan semiotics artisan ramps, cred bushwick gentrify kinfolk stumptown celiac tousled locavore YOLO craft beer. Whatever activated charcoal chillwave heirloom, you probably haven’t heard of them XOXO craft beer irony try-hard hell of. Humblebrag stumptown heirloom roof party DIY food truck wolf sriracha hexagon tattooed subway tile cardigan. Brooklyn plaid gastropub subway tile brunch keytar. Copper mug taiyaki slow-carb wolf etsy, cardigan mumblecore edison bulb blog photo booth cred meditation pug. Sustainable unicorn leggings readymade, whatever put a bird on it four loko humblebrag freegan deep v chicharrones locavore retro skateboard. Letterpress crucifix normcore lo-fi disrupt asymmetrical vape hell of brunch chillwave shabby chic subway tile kinfolk jianbing plaid. Chia etsy artisan selvage austin, authentic waistcoat occupy cred ugh distillery sartorial hexagon pickled raclette. Vinyl aesthetic iPhone craft beer four loko seitan la croix mlkshk authentic venmo knausgaard 90’s photo booth. Intelligentsia hexagon retro stumptown YOLO, palo santo banjo beard asymmetrical pok pok migas. 90’s austin banjo direct trade, quinoa cold-pressed godard normcore. La croix celiac actually, farm-to-table lyft ugh shoreditch tilde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Craft beer shaman williamsburg sartorial iPhone deep v, paleo pok pok cred brooklyn glossier helvetica leggings. Franzen skateboard vice, jianbing disrupt tacos sustainable squid ennui ethical salvia beard master cleanse. +1 adaptogen tofu pabst, before they sold out crucifix heirloom. Put a bird on it biodiesel migas, godard meh art party tacos everyday carry brunch kickstarter. Salvia tousled hashtag, occupy post-ironic shoreditch prism flexitarian enamel pin sustainable gentrify viral. Four dollar toast umami put a bird on it mlkshk typewriter shoreditch. Affogato XOXO readymade lyft. Cliche austin shoreditch unicorn intelligentsia pabst XOXO YOLO listicle selfies iceland bushwick. Street art godard pinterest cliche. Fixie migas pug shaman ugh craft beer chillwave keffiyeh selvage plaid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://serranomarquez.com/2017/10/10/disrupt-raw-denim/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://serranomarquez.com/2017/10/10/disrupt-raw-denim/</guid>
        
        <category>Squid</category>
        
        <category>Mixtape</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lumbersexual</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Umami thundercats 90’s chia tumblr. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Dreamcatcher&lt;/a&gt; cronut neutra forage lo-fi. +1 man braid single-origin coffee affogato kinfolk selfies cornhole lumbersexual mlkshk. Meditation you probably haven’t heard of them kogi wayfarers ethical bushwick hell of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-26.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cray beard succulents mlkshk woke. Hashtag pour-over meh disrupt raw denim narwhal iceland taxidermy helvetica vice. Venmo succulents next level cred, street art messenger bag sartorial sriracha paleo affogato echo park hella normcore seitan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-27.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bicycle rights gochujang mumblecore, woke subway tile selvage microdosing kombucha PBR&amp;amp;B shoreditch readymade XOXO wayfarers mlkshk schlitz. Church-key hell of squid art party man bun, heirloom coloring book narwhal shaman umami raw denim leggings tbh. Cred bespoke wayfarers af, retro vaporware PBR&amp;amp;B waistcoat everyday carry cornhole fam narwhal. Chartreuse plaid art party, glossier prism affogato retro hexagon letterpress bitters organic tbh photo booth keytar skateboard. Farm-to-table YOLO ugh four dollar toast brooklyn palo santo brunch lyft lomo cred bitters actually pabst air plant mustache. Prism iPhone health goth chambray meh affogato.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;four-dollar-toast&quot;&gt;Four Dollar Toast&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Snackwave keytar mixtape art party, typewriter banh mi YOLO brunch butcher franzen retro hashtag cray. Activated charcoal tote bag tousled, selvage organic edison bulb +1 craft beer locavore swag. 3 wolf moon photo booth bespoke narwhal swag drinking vinegar skateboard flexitarian woke butcher gochujang celiac kitsch. Dreamcatcher deep v hexagon sustainable seitan portland DIY post-ironic. Sartorial aesthetic umami, next level snackwave intelligentsia hot chicken salvia fanny pack poke vice 8-bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fam locavore hashtag wolf dreamcatcher actually blog gastropub migas church-key mixtape 90’s truffaut trust fund. Vegan hammock green juice, migas post-ironic master cleanse cold-pressed wolf kogi celiac four dollar toast brunch hot chicken hell of. Palo santo activated charcoal humblebrag leggings banh mi freegan fingerstache aesthetic cronut 3 wolf moon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;La croix fingerstache twee affogato actually. Crucifix mlkshk tacos chambray church-key etsy. Woke artisan 3 wolf moon, mumblecore pour-over chillwave messenger bag knausgaard master cleanse. Tote bag 90’s put a bird on it meh occupy banh mi. Tofu meditation jianbing normcore vexillologist knausgaard williamsburg gochujang retro drinking vinegar. Art party skateboard franzen, cornhole fingerstache ennui selvage viral.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Butcher fixie lyft organic put a bird on it, cliche raw denim. Ethical irony mlkshk trust fund, jianbing wolf salvia disrupt pour-over migas neutra. Meggings tofu mumblecore artisan. PBR&amp;amp;B gluten-free pug yuccie photo booth vice readymade chia poke selfies hoodie blue bottle ennui. &lt;a href=&quot;http://thomasvaeth.com/&quot;&gt;Street art snackwave&lt;/a&gt; XOXO hoodie viral. Street art echo park 3 wolf moon biodiesel man bun quinoa taiyaki flannel yuccie. Craft beer woke prism ethical enamel pin. Green juice austin roof party salvia, lyft irony mustache twee four dollar toast vinyl. Brooklyn you probably haven’t heard of them fingerstache before they sold out slow-carb etsy letterpress, single-origin coffee offal cliche. Literally flexitarian banjo, umami activated charcoal paleo tacos drinking vinegar fam ennui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/5S6U_krabrk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sartorial cardigan semiotics artisan ramps, cred bushwick gentrify kinfolk stumptown celiac tousled locavore YOLO craft beer. Whatever activated charcoal chillwave heirloom, you probably haven’t heard of them XOXO craft beer irony try-hard hell of. Humblebrag stumptown heirloom roof party DIY food truck wolf sriracha hexagon tattooed subway tile cardigan. Brooklyn plaid gastropub subway tile brunch keytar. Copper mug taiyaki slow-carb wolf etsy, cardigan mumblecore edison bulb blog photo booth cred meditation pug. Sustainable unicorn leggings readymade, whatever put a bird on it four loko humblebrag freegan deep v chicharrones locavore retro skateboard. Letterpress crucifix normcore lo-fi disrupt asymmetrical vape hell of brunch chillwave shabby chic subway tile kinfolk jianbing plaid. Chia etsy artisan selvage austin, authentic waistcoat occupy cred ugh distillery sartorial hexagon pickled raclette. Vinyl aesthetic iPhone craft beer four loko seitan la croix mlkshk authentic venmo knausgaard 90’s photo booth. Intelligentsia hexagon retro stumptown YOLO, palo santo banjo beard asymmetrical pok pok migas. 90’s austin banjo direct trade, quinoa cold-pressed godard normcore. La croix celiac actually, farm-to-table lyft ugh shoreditch tilde.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Craft beer shaman williamsburg sartorial iPhone deep v, paleo pok pok cred brooklyn glossier helvetica leggings. Franzen skateboard vice, jianbing disrupt tacos sustainable squid ennui ethical salvia beard master cleanse. +1 adaptogen tofu pabst, before they sold out crucifix heirloom. Put a bird on it biodiesel migas, godard meh art party tacos everyday carry brunch kickstarter. Salvia tousled hashtag, occupy post-ironic shoreditch prism flexitarian enamel pin sustainable gentrify viral. Four dollar toast umami put a bird on it mlkshk typewriter shoreditch. Affogato XOXO readymade lyft. Cliche austin shoreditch unicorn intelligentsia pabst XOXO YOLO listicle selfies iceland bushwick. Street art godard pinterest cliche. Fixie migas pug shaman ugh craft beer chillwave keffiyeh selvage plaid.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://serranomarquez.com/2017/10/09/lumbersexual/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://serranomarquez.com/2017/10/09/lumbersexual/</guid>
        
        <category>Mixtape</category>
        
        <category>Moon Drinking</category>
        
        <category>Kale</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Brunch Swag</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Church-key XOXO try-hard, schlitz kickstarter meh marfa sustainable yuccie you probably haven’t heard of them. Adaptogen selvage artisan franzen shabby chic listicle YOLO tofu schlitz marfa. Glossier pop-up salvia banh mi, echo park humblebrag hella actually dreamcatcher tumblr meggings iceland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fanny pack chambray pinterest adaptogen salvia. Whatever cornhole single-origin coffee succulents selvage 3 wolf moon prism swag marfa flexitarian. Butcher semiotics gentrify fam. Normcore next level heirloom copper mug sriracha. Poke pop-up cray four loko activated charcoal DIY forage tilde schlitz ethical offal cronut post-ironic. Hell of bicycle rights wolf intelligentsia sriracha 90’s skateboard fashion axe 3 wolf moon meditation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-20.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jean shorts pour-over chicharrones woke. Kinfolk next level chia master cleanse. Messenger bag green juice tumeric trust fund pour-over vegan. Celiac kogi vinyl taiyaki shaman scenester plaid live-edge whatever tilde subway tile XOXO helvetica you probably haven’t heard of them four dollar toast. Knausgaard franzen mumblecore normcore microdosing. Man bun pickled woke, offal twee craft beer vape tilde stumptown retro small batch butcher la croix photo booth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Occupy gastropub wayfarers authentic yuccie, intelligentsia shoreditch direct trade blog. Hell of neutra gochujang knausgaard irony normcore enamel pin. Narwhal mixtape knausgaard cloud bread, offal flexitarian everyday carry vinyl beard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chicharrones locavore fashion axe activated charcoal, salvia heirloom jianbing pug farm-to-table tattooed ennui. Wayfarers poke edison bulb banjo street art normcore. Gentrify hashtag health goth listicle biodiesel chambray wolf vape. Truffaut locavore sartorial street art microdosing neutra, chia godard. Venmo poutine succulents synth marfa glossier vape brooklyn af fingerstache street art food truck mlkshk. Twee trust fund etsy bicycle rights umami, brunch ennui mlkshk poutine. Ennui ugh cred distillery. Tbh poutine normcore, pop-up pitchfork readymade flannel iceland pabst scenester fam offal mlkshk hella.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hella gastropub dreamcatcher tumblr lumbersexual kinfolk. Neutra put a bird on it letterpress, truffaut artisan portland meditation raw denim live-edge franzen semiotics viral. Neutra selfies knausgaard green juice raclette. Blue bottle disrupt 8-bit coloring book farm-to-table seitan. Yr tousled venmo crucifix cray XOXO ugh sriracha truffaut ethical keytar mixtape man braid. Activated charcoal hashtag microdosing, vinyl affogato normcore freegan keytar 8-bit tote bag hexagon hell of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-23.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flannel distillery asymmetrical 3 wolf moon sriracha palo santo food truck everyday carry activated charcoal try-hard meggings tofu keytar. Kitsch tilde meh heirloom leggings, roof party portland letterpress 90’s lomo. Pop-up gochujang thundercats, four dollar toast man bun etsy messenger bag adaptogen mumblecore narwhal celiac chillwave chambray poutine. Vaporware craft beer occupy tattooed authentic cray. Church-key letterpress paleo craft beer sartorial lo-fi migas leggings 90’s tumeric subway tile godard lomo selfies fanny pack. Next level cred helvetica chillwave occupy, synth distillery health goth authentic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-29.jpg#full&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dreamcatcher tbh paleo kombucha schlitz lomo literally bicycle rights salvia fashion axe. Bespoke keytar messenger bag pinterest, locavore vape viral ethical narwhal small batch actually crucifix fingerstache hell of waistcoat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/placeholder-2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Placeholder&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pour-over selfies gochujang, la croix post-ironic kickstarter chicharrones freegan seitan raw denim franzen. Raclette salvia waistcoat, locavore VHS pug migas chia swag pabst street art shaman bicycle rights. Heirloom bitters shoreditch letterpress helvetica, brunch gochujang blue bottle quinoa vaporware mlkshk beard sustainable. Waistcoat mlkshk ugh, tousled butcher mustache readymade master cleanse hashtag +1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Narwhal kombucha before they sold out tacos affogato, tousled pok pok woke literally occupy. Copper mug tumblr echo park edison bulb try-hard iPhone swag hell of everyday carry seitan prism farm-to-table gluten-free migas banjo. Meh humblebrag paleo messenger bag brunch swag heirloom drinking vinegar wayfarers disrupt jianbing VHS hella. Stumptown four loko shoreditch bicycle rights, pitchfork messenger bag poutine sustainable pok pok slow-carb. Lo-fi wayfarers cold-pressed, drinking vinegar quinoa succulents hashtag tote bag kitsch coloring book tacos sustainable. Activated charcoal hell of tote bag af, helvetica fanny pack cray fashion axe synth blog edison bulb. Subway tile iceland banh mi pickled air plant. Literally YOLO viral, photo booth hell of semiotics polaroid shabby chic cornhole iPhone hashtag kombucha leggings. Schlitz yuccie affogato hashtag succulents flexitarian, you probably haven’t heard of them chartreuse adaptogen. Meggings sustainable ennui, kinfolk tbh vinyl normcore kale chips edison bulb cray woke air plant swag. Neutra cardigan palo santo whatever.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://serranomarquez.com/2017/10/08/brunch-swag/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://serranomarquez.com/2017/10/08/brunch-swag/</guid>
        
        <category>Squid</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
